kerbalspaceport.com 2014-04-09

# Privacy Policy | Kerbal SpacePort

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?** ****

We collect information from you when you sign up on our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropiate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, country, and telephone.  You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?** ****

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond your individual needs).
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions
  * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.
  * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product information, etc.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?** ****

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

**DO WE USE COOKIES?** ****

We do not use cookies.

**DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?** ****

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropiate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

**ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY** ****

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**YOUR CONSENT** ****

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy](http://kerbalspaceprogram.com/privacypolicy.php#)[policy](http://kerbalspaceprogram.com/privacypolicy.php#).

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY** ****

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 01/10/2012

**CONTACTING US** ****

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Zamora 196  
Condesa, Mexico City 06140  
MEX
